Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Role-Playing Games, 1972-2009
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Modules, Manuals, and Campaign Volumes, 1973-2009 and undated, (2399 volumes)
  - General Games
    - A Fistful of Turkeys. Published by Cedar Park, TX: Some Turkey Games, 1981., D04382324Q (Box BG 39, Volume 672)
    - A Game of Thrones: d20-based Open Gaming RPG. Published by no place: White Wolf Publishing, 2005., D04373203M (Box BG 39, Volume 112)
    - A Modeler's Guide to Ancient and Medieval Ships to 1650. Published by Dana Point, CA: Moonraker Publications, 1981., D04403751O (Box BG 39, Volume 1580)
    - Abyss. Published by Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc., 1980., D04382329V (Box BG 39, Volume 677)
    - Aliens: Adventure Game. Published by Pasadena, CA: Leading Edge Games, 1991., D04382718X (Box BG 39, Volume 1347)
    - All the Worlds' Monsters. Published by Albany, CA: The Chaosium, 1977., D04405649W (Box BG 39, Volume M3)
    - All the Worlds' Monsters, 2nd ed. Published by Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc., 1981., D04403722M (Box BG 39, Volume 1620)
    - All the Worlds' Monsters, Vol. II. Published by Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc., 1977., D04403797Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1619)
    - All the Worlds' Monsters, Vol. III. Published by Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc., 1980., D04403721L (Box BG 39, Volume 1618)
    - Amazon Mutual Wants You!, Vol. I. Published by Abilene, TX: Dragon Tree Press, 1982., D04403803M (Box BG 39, Volume 1628)
    - Amber. Published by Detroit, MI: Phage Press, 1991., D04382712R (Box BG 39, Volume 1369)
    - Annihilator and One World. Published by Austin, TX: Metagaming, 1979., D04382336T (Box BG 39, Volume 684)
    - Arden: A Complete Kingdom. Published by Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1979., D04383026Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1349)
    - At Rapier's Point. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1993., D04403621K (Box BG 39, Volume 1445)
    - Authentic Thaumaturgy. Published by Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc., 1978., D04403904O (Box BG 39, Volume 1722)
    - Barsoomian Battle Manual. Published by Dallas, TX: Heritage Models, Inc., 1978., D04403861Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1680)
    - Basic Role-Playing. Published by Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc., 1981., D04382825W (Box BG 39, Volume 1080)
    - Battle for Basra. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1991., D04405792V (Box BG 39, Volume 1795)
    - Black Hole. Published by Austin, TX: Metagaming, 1978., D04382331O (Box BG 39, Volume 679)
    - Book of Fantasy Miniatures. Published by Rockville, MD: Phoenix Games, 1978., D04403944S (Box BG 39, Volume 1764)
    - Book of Plots, Vol. I: Tavern Tales. Published by Abilene, TX: Dragon Tree Press, 1983., D04403772R (Box BG 39, Volume 1585)
    - Building Complex Series 1: Corporation Building. Published by Seeker Gaming Systems, 1991., D04563677 (Box BG 39, Volume 1954)
    - Building Complex Series 2: Research Facility. Published by Seeker Gaming Systems, 1992., D04563679/ (Box BG 39, Volume 1955)
    - Bunnies and Burrows: The Fantasy World of Intelligent Rabbits. Published by Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1976., D04403855T (Box BG 39, Volume 1674)
    - Campaign Law: Guidelines for Gamemasters. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1982., D04382814U (Box BG 39, Volume 1086)
    - Carse: Urban Aid for Fantasy Roleplaying. Published by Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc., 1986., D04403926S (Box BG 39, Volume 1744)
    - Castle Arcania. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1985., D02340966U (Box BG 39, Volume M2)
    - Castle Book II. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1981., D04403745R (Box BG 39, Volume 1555)
    - Circle of Ice. Published by Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc., 1980., D04382330N (Box BG 39, Volume 678)
    - Cities, 2nd ed. Published by San Diego, CA: Midkemia Press, 1981., D04403796X (Box BG 39, Volume 1613)
    - Cities: A Gamemaster's Guide. Published by San Diego, CA: Stephen Abrams, 1979., D04403774T (Box BG 39, Volume 1587)
    - Cities: Create and Explore your own Fantasy Communities. Published by Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc., 1986., D04403927T (Box BG 39, Volume 1745)
    - City of Terrors. Published by Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc., 1978., D04403877X (Box BG 39, Volume 1699)
    - City State of the World Emperor. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1982., D04403887Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1692)
    - CityBook I: Butcher, Baker, Candlestick Maker. Published by Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc., 1982., D04403825Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1646)
    - CityBook II: Port o' Call. Published by Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc., 1984., D04403822N (Box BG 39, Volume 1643)
    - CityBook III: Deadly Nightside. Published by Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc., 1987., D04403824P (Box BG 39, Volume 1645)
    - Cloudland. Published by Grenadier Models, Inc., 1984., D04382767. (Box BG 39, Volume 1139)
    - Corsair! A Game of Piracy and Plunder. Published by unknown, 1977., D04405648V (Box BG 39, Volume M4)
    - Corsairs of Tallibar. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1982., D04403681Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1505)
    - Dimensions and Doors. Published by Peterborough, NH: Rider Fantasy Creations, 1979., D04403870Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1689)
    - Dream Park. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1992., D04383057U (Box BG 39, Volume 1415)
    - Druids of Doom. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1982., D04403677V (Box BG 39, Volume 1500)
    - Duel Arcane. Published by Gaithersburg, MD: Gamelords Ltd., 1980., D02340966U (Box BG 39, Volume M2)
    - Dungeon Décor: Scenery for Role-playing Games and Dioramas. Published by Agawam, MA: Falchion Products, 1978., D04405650O (Box BG 39, Volume M5)
    - Fantastic Personalities. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1981., D04403736R (Box BG 39, Volume 1546)
    - Faster than Light. Published by Madison Hts, Michigan: Tri Tac Inc., 1982., D04405649W (Box BG 39, Volume M3)
    - F'deckFo's Tomb. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1981., D04403667U (Box BG 39, Volume 1492)
    - Field Guide to Ecounters vol 2. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1982., D04403933Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1751)
    - Fire, Hack and Run: Universal Skirmish Rules. Published by Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1979., D04403811L (Box BG 39, Volume 1636)
    - Fringeworthy. Published by Madison Hts, MI: Tri Tac, Inc., 1982., D04403818S (Box BG 39, Volume 1659)
    - Game Design, Vol. I: Theory and Practice. Published by Austin, TX: Steve Jackson Games, 1981., D04403787X (Box BG 39, Volume 1603)
    - Gear Krieg: Two-Fisted Pulp Superscience in a World At War!. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 2000., D04563951X (Box BG 39, Volume 2205)
    - Gladiators. Published by Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1975., D04403874U (Box BG 39, Volume 1696)
    - Glory Hole Dwarven Mine. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1981., D04403738T (Box BG 39, Volume 1548)
    - Goblin Lake. Published by Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc., 1979., D04382333Q (Box BG 39, Volume 681)
    - Grimtooth's Traps Too: A Game-Master's Aid. Published by Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc., 1982., D04382755Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1067)
    - Grimtooth's Traps: A Game-Master's Aid. Published by Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc., 1981., D04382756Z (Box BG 39, Volume 1066)
    - Guide to the City State. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1976., D04405648V (Box BG 39, Volume M4)
    - Gunfights in the Spirit of the Old West. Published by Raleigh, NC: Argon Games, 1980., D02340966U (Box BG 39, Volume M2)
    - Gunslinger. Published by Sarasota, FL: R. Sartore and Associates, 1978., D04405648V (Box BG 39, Volume M4)
    - Heart of the Sunken Lands. Published by San Diego, CA: Midkemia Press, 1983., D04403776V (Box BG 39, Volume 1590)
    - Heroes: Unlimited. Published by Detroit, MI: Palladium Books, 1984., D04382752V (Box BG 39, Volume 1085)
    - Heroic Expeditions. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1981., D04403934R (Box BG 39, Volume 1752)
    - High Colonies. Published by Vancouver, BC: Waterford Publishing House, Ltd., 1988., D04383027R (Box BG 39, Volume 1350)
    - High Ranger Guard. Published by Charlotte, NC: Entertainment Concepts, Inc., 1982., D04403806P (Box BG 39, Volume 1631)
    - Holy War. Published by Austin, TX: Metagaming, 1979., D04382332P (Box BG 39, Volume 680)
    - Hong Kong Action Theatre!. Published by Lawrence, KS: Event Horizons Productions, 1996., D04403620J (Box BG 39, Volume 1444)
    - Ice War. Published by Austin, TX: Metagaming, 1978., D04382337U (Box BG 39, Volume 685)
    - In Search of Kelandor's Gold. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1982., D04403641M (Box BG 39, Volume 1465)
    - Invasion of the Air-Eaters. Published by Austin, TX: Metagaming, 1979., D04382339W (Box BG 39, Volume 687)
    - Ironhoof Highlands. Published by Decatur, IL: Group One Games, 1981., D04403763R (Box BG 39, Volume 1573)
    - Jonril: Gateway to the Sunken Lands. Published by San Diego, CA: Midkemia Press, 1982., D04403775U (Box BG 39, Volume 1588)
    - Junta: The Game of Power, Intrigue, Money and Revolution. Published by New York, NY: Creative Wargames Workshop Inc., 1979., D04405648V (Box BG 39, Volume M4)
    - Killer: The Game of Assassination. Published by Austin, TX: Steve Jackson Games, 1981., D04382834W (Box BG 39, Volume 1072)
    - Kung Fu 2100. Published by Austin, TX: Steve Jackson Games, 1980., D04382326S (Box BG 39, Volume 674)
    - Lionheart: Living in History: England 1190 AD. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Publications, 1987., D04382591W (Box BG 39, Volume 962)
    - Lords of the Middle Sea. Published by Albany, CA: The Chaosium, 1978., D04405648V (Box BG 39, Volume M4)
    - Lythia. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Games, 1985., D043828990 (Box BG 39, Volume 1197)
    - Master Book Companion. Published by Honesdale, PA: West End Games, undated., D04254445S (Box BG 39, Volume 230)
    - Master Book: With the Worlds of Indiana Jones and Bloodshadows. Published by Honesdale, PA: West End Games, 1994., D03574344U (Box BG 39, Volume 595)
    - Masters of Mind. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1981., D04403670O (Box BG 39, Volume 1495)
    - Metamorphosis Alpha. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1976., D04403856U (Box BG 39, Volume 1675)
    - Miniature Rules. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1989., D03805785- (Box BG 39, Volume 523)
    - Mini-System 2: Character Role Playing. Published by Washington, D.C.: Ragnarok Enterprises, 1981., D04403911M (Box BG 39, Volume 1729)
    - Monday Morning Manager. Published by Gaithersburg, MD: Gamelords Ltd., 1980., D02340966U (Box BG 39, Volume M2)
    - Monsters! Monsters!. Published by Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc., 1979., D04382835X (Box BG 39, Volume 1074)
    - Monstrous Compendium: Appendix. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04382446V (Box BG 39, Volume 818)
    - Mountain of Mystery. Published by Englewood, CO: Dimension Six, Inc., 1980., D04403867W (Box BG 39, Volume 1686)
    - Mug Book: The Game of Street Crimes. Published by Denver, CO: Power Play Games, 1984., D04403889- (Box BG 39, Volume 1694)
    - Murder in Irliss. Published by Reston, VA: Reston Publishing Company, Inc., 1982., D04400521G (Box BG 39, Volume 1793)
    - Naka. Published by Mission, KS: Bearhug Publications, 1979., D04405650O (Box BG 39, Volume M5)
    - Noir. Published by Archon Gaming, Inc., 1996., D04382714T (Box BG 39, Volume 1357)
    - Nomad Gods. Published by Albany, CA: The Chaosium, 1977., D04405648V (Box BG 39, Volume M4)
    - Odysseus: Legendry and Mythology. Published by Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1980., D04382829- (Box BG 39, Volume 1065)
    - Ogre. Published by Austin, TX: Metagaming, 1977., D04382341P (Box BG 39, Volume 689)
    - One-Page Bulge. Published by Austin, TX: Steve Jackson Games, 1980., D04382325R (Box BG 39, Volume 673)
    - Overland Ecounters: Fifth through the Eighth Levels. Published by Oakland, CA: The Fantasy Factory, 1979., D04405648V (Box BG 39, Volume M4)
    - Overland Ecounters: First through the Forth Levels. Published by Oakland, CA: The Fantasy Factory, 1979., D04405648V (Box BG 39, Volume M4)
    - Palladium RPG Book III: Adventures on the High Seas. Published by Detroit, MI: Palladium Books, 1987., D04382716V (Box BG 39, Volume 1351)
    - Pirates of Hagrost. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1982., D04403747T (Box BG 39, Volume 1557)
    - Places of Mystery II: Alluring Alcoves. Published by Bath, ME: The Companions, Inc., 1983., D04403769X (Box BG 39, Volume 1579)
    - Places of Mystery III: Sylvan Settings. Published by Bath, ME: The Companions, Inc., 1983., D04403782S (Box BG 39, Volume 1598)
    - Prey of Darkness. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1982., D04403756T (Box BG 39, Volume 1564)
    - Race to High Adventure Through Icy Arctic Seas: Icebergs Minigame. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1982., D02340966U (Box BG 39, Volume M2)
    - Raid on Iran. Published by Austin, TX: Steve Jackson Games, 1980., D04382323P (Box BG 39, Volume 671)
    - Raiders and Traders: the Heroic Age of Greece. Published by Albany, CA: The Chaosium, 1979., D04405648V (Box BG 39, Volume M4)
    - Rapier and Dagger. Published by Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1978., D04403872S (Box BG 39, Volume 1691)
    - Ravenlon: Danger in the Dark Forest. Published by Charlotte, NC: Entertainment Concepts, Inc., 1982., D04403810K (Box BG 39, Volume 1635)
    - Ravenscrag. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1981., D04403701J (Box BG 39, Volume 1503)
    - Recon. Published by Lincoln, AR: RPG, Inc., 1982., D04382828Z (Box BG 39, Volume 1077)
    - Reich Star. Published by Charlotte, NC: Creative Encounters, 1990., D04382717W (Box BG 39, Volume 1348)
    - Reich: The Iron Dream of German Unification. Published by Albany, CA: The Chaosium, 1979., D04405648V (Box BG 39, Volume M4)
    - Relive the Battle at the Alamo with Famous Frontier Heroes: Remember the Alamo Minigame. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1982., D02340966U (Box BG 39, Volume M2)
    - Restormel. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1981., D04403728S (Box BG 39, Volume 1538)
    - Revolt on Antares: Science Fiction Minigame. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1981., D02340966U (Box BG 39, Volume M2)
    - Rivets. Published by Austin, TX: Metagaming, 1977., D04382338V (Box BG 39, Volume 686)
    - Sage: Age of Heroes Minigame. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1981., D02340966U (Box BG 39, Volume M2)
    - Search for the Crystal Sword. Published by Charlotte, NC: Entertainment Concepts, Inc., 1982., D04403807Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1632)
    - Search for the Lost City: A Jungle Adventure. Published by Charlotte, NC: Entertainment Concepts, Inc., 1982., D04403809S (Box BG 39, Volume 1634)
    - Shield Maidens of Sea Rule. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1982., D04403746S (Box BG 39, Volume 1556)
    - Society of Sorcery. Published by Charlotte, NC: Entertainment Concepts, Inc., 1982., D04403805O (Box BG 39, Volume 1630)
    - Space Warrior. Published by Raleigh, NC: Argon Games, 1980., D02340966U (Box BG 39, Volume M2)
    - Spacefarers Guide to Alien Monsters. Published by Rockville, MD: Phoenix Games, 1979., D04403833P (Box BG 39, Volume 1654)
    - Spacefarers Guide to Alien Races. Published by Rockville, MD: Phoenix Games, 1979., D04403815P (Box BG 39, Volume 1655)
    - Spacefarers Guide to Planets: Sector One. Published by Rockville, MD: Phoenix Games, 1978., D04403834Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1656)
    - Spacefarers Guide to Sector Two. Published by Rockville, MD: Phoenix Games, 1979., D04403816Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1657)
    - Starfaring. Published by Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc., 1976., D04403853R (Box BG 39, Volume 1672)
    - Starships and Spacemen. Published by Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1978., D04403854S (Box BG 39, Volume 1673)
    - Supergame. Published by Santa Monica, CA: Dag Design, 1980., D04382833V (Box BG 39, Volume 1071)
    - Superhero 2044. Published by no city: Gamescience, Inc., 1977., D04403859X (Box BG 39, Volume 1678)
    - Swordplay. Published by unknown, undated., D02340966U (Box BG 39, Volume M2)
    - Tegal Manor. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1977., D04403739U (Box BG 39, Volume 1549)
    - Temple, Book 1. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1981., D04403984W (Box BG 39, Volume 1776)
    - The Adventure of the Jade Jaguar. Published by Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc., 1983., D04382836Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1075)
    - The Astrogators Chartbook. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1980., D04403980S (Box BG 39, Volume 1772)
    - The Black Tower. Published by San Diego, CA: Midkemia Press, 1981., D04403784U (Box BG 39, Volume 1600)
    - The Book of Shamans. Published by Rockville, MD: Phoenix Games, 1978., D04403709R (Box BG 39, Volume 1570)
    - The Book of Treasure. Published by Rockville, MD: Phoenix Games, 1978., D04403712L (Box BG 39, Volume 1572)
    - The Book of Treasure Maps III. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1982., D04403640L (Box BG 39, Volume 1464)
    - The City of Carse. Published by San Diego, CA: Midkemia Press, 1980., D04403786W (Box BG 39, Volume 1602)
    - The City of Carse, 2nd ed.. Published by San Diego, CA: Midkemia Press, 1980., D04403626P (Box BG 39, Volume 1457)
    - The Compendium of Weapons, Armour and Castles. Published by Detroit, MI: Palladium Books, 1989., D04403717Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1614)
    - The Compleat Fantasist: How to Convert the Major Fantasy Role Playing Systems to Each Other. Published by Englewood, CO: Dimension Six, Inc., 1980., D04403762Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1571)
    - The Complete Warlock. Published by Long Beach, CA: Balboa Game Co., 1978., D04403800J (Box BG 39, Volume 1623)
    - The Curse on Hareth. Published by Bath, ME: The Companions Inc., 1982., D04405649W (Box BG 39, Volume M3)
    - The D6 System: The Customizable Roleplaying Game. Published by Honesdale, PA: West End Games, 1996., D04254456U (Box BG 39, Volume 242)
    - The Demon Pits of Caeldo. Published by Gaithersburg, MD: Gamelords, Ltd., 1983., D04382876 (Box BG 39, Volume 1172)
    - The Dungeon Masters Survival Kit. Published by Portland, OR: Sage Lore Productions Inc., undated., D04405648V (Box BG 39, Volume M4)
    - The Emerald Tablet. Published by New York, NY: Creative Wargames Workshop, Inc., 1977., D04403875V (Box BG 39, Volume 1697)
    - The Fantasy Cartographer's Field Book. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1980., D04403981T (Box BG 39, Volume 1773)
    - The Fighter. Published by Killeen, TX: Martian Game Modules, 1979., D04405648V (Box BG 39, Volume M4)
    - The First Fantasy Campaign. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1977., D04403812M (Box BG 39, Volume 1637)
    - The Giant Robot Role Playing and Battle Game: Robot Warriors (#27). Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1986., D04563825X (Box BG 39, Volume 2129)
    - The Gods vs. Chaos in Deadly Final Conflict: Viking Gods Minigame. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1982., D02340966U (Box BG 39, Volume M2)
    - The Handbook of Traps and Tricks. Published by Abilene, TX: Dragon Tree Press, 1981., D04403907R (Box BG 39, Volume 1725)
    - The Legacy of Zorro. Published by no city: Fusion Labs Group, 2001., D04403783T (Box BG 39, Volume 1599)
    - The Lost Abbey of Calthonwey. Published by Rockville, MD: Phoenix Games, 1979., D04382879+ (Box BG 39, Volume 1173)
    - The Manual of Aurania, 2nd ed. Published by no city: Gary Switzer, undated., D04403801K (Box BG 39, Volume 1626)
    - The Mines of Keridav. Published by Rockville, MD: Phoenix Games, 1979., D04382874- (Box BG 39, Volume 1170)
    - The Mines of Keridav. Published by Gaithersburg, MD: Gamelords, Ltd., 1983., D04382768 (Box BG 39, Volume 1140)
    - The Monkey God's Curse. Published by Bellflower, CA: Balboa Game Company Co., undated., D04403761P (Box BG 39, Volume 1569)
    - The Munchkin's Guide to Power Gaming. Published by no city: Steve Jackson Games, 1999., D03804360O (Box BG 39, Volume 722)
    - The New Ysgarth Rules. Published by Washington, D.C.: Ragnarok Enterprises, 1980., D04403885W (Box BG 39, Volume 1707)
    - The Nine Doctrines of Darkness. Published by Englewood, CO: Dimension Six, Inc., 1980., D04403865U (Box BG 39, Volume 1684)
    - The Official Superhero Adventure Game. Published by Dayton, OH: Brian Phillips, 1981., D04405648V (Box BG 39, Volume M4)
    - The Ogre Book. Published by Austin, TX: Steve Jackson Games, 1982., D04403788Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1604)
    - The Palladium Book of Contemporary Weapons. Published by Detroit, MI: Palladium Books, 1984., D04563904V (Box BG 39, Volume 2323)
    - The Palladium Book of European Castles. Published by Detroit, MI: Palladium Books, 1985., D04563903U (Box BG 39, Volume 2322)
    - The Palladium Book of Exotic Weapons. Published by Detroit, MI: Palladium Books, 1984., D04563908Z (Box BG 39, Volume 2327)
    - The Palladium Book of Weapons and Armour. Published by Detroit, MI: Palladium Books, 1981., D04563907Y (Box BG 39, Volume 2326)
    - The Palladium Book of Weapons and Assassins. Published by Detroit, MI: Palladium Books, 1983., D04563905W (Box BG 39, Volume 2324)
    - The Palladium Book of Weapons and Castles. Published by Detroit, MI: Palladium Books, 1982., D04563902T (Box BG 39, Volume 2321)
    - The Palladium Book of Weapons and Castles of the Orient. Published by Detroit, MI: Palladium Books, 1984., D04563906X (Box BG 39, Volume 2325)
    - The Palladium Role-Playing Game. Published by Detroit, MI: Palladium Books, 1983., D04382593Y (Box BG 39, Volume 964)
    - The Palladium RPG: Book II: Old Ones. Published by Detroit, MI: Palladium Books, 1984., D04382592X (Box BG 39, Volume 963)
    - The Plateau Capital of Evil. Published by Charlotte, NC: Entertainment Concepts, Inc., 1982., D04403808R (Box BG 39, Volume 1633)
    - The Serpent Islands. Published by Mobile, AL: North Pole Publications, 1983., D04382871X (Box BG 39, Volume 1167)
    - The Staff of Fanon. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Publications, 1988., D04382913U (Box BG 39, Volume 1180)
    - The Temple to Athena. Published by Englewood, CO: Dimension Six, Inc., 1980., D04403866V (Box BG 39, Volume 1685)
    - The Tower of Indomitable Circumstance. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1981., D04403668V (Box BG 39, Volume 1493)
    - The Warlock Menagerie. Published by Long Beach, CA: Balboa Game Co., 1980., D04403799- (Box BG 39, Volume 1622)
    - The Wizard's Aide. Published by Chula Vista, CA: Matt Whalley, 1977., D04403905P (Box BG 39, Volume 1723)
    - The Ythri. Published by Austin, TX: Metagaming Concepts, 1975., D04403932P (Box BG 39, Volume 1750)
    - They've Invaded Pleasantville: Game of Alien Infiltration. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1981., D02340966U (Box BG 39, Volume M2)
    - Timelag. Published by Manchester, CT: Gameshop Inc., 1980., D02340966U (Box BG 39, Volume M2)
    - Tomorrow the World: Fire and Movement. Published by Salinas, CA: Cummins Enterprises, 1989., D04405648V (Box BG 39, Volume M4)
    - Toon. Published by Austin, TX: Steve Jackson Games, 1984., D04382821S (Box BG 39, Volume 1084)
    - Toon Strikes Again. Published by Austin, TX: Steve Jackson Games, 1985., D04382823U (Box BG 39, Volume 1082)
    - Tournament Jousting: a Combat Simulation. Published by Mission, KS: Bearhug Publications, 1979., D04405650O (Box BG 39, Volume M5)
    - Towns of the Outlands. Published by San Diego, CA: Midkemia Press, 1981., D04403781R (Box BG 39, Volume 1597)
    - Treasury of Archaic Names, Vol. I. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1979., D04403632M (Box BG 39, Volume 1462)
    - Troy. Published by Albany, CA: The Chaosium, 1977., D04405648V (Box BG 39, Volume M4)